Sparks Photographs
undated
- Photographs, 1860-1997
  - Group of Navy soldiers from the U.S. Naval Reserve, 1944-1950; UNRS-P2017-13_1048; Photographic print; 10 x 8 1/8; The top of the print is partially ripped. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a platoon of the U.S. Naval Reserve posing in front of an air blimp. In the background is a hanger. No identification.
  - Squadron of U.S. Naval Reserve, 1950-09; UNRS-P2017-13_1049; Photographic print; 10 x 8 1/8 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a Naval Air Reserve in front of a plane and standing on the wings of the plane. Caption on front: U.S. Naval Air Reserve Squadron VP-871 ATD NAS Oakland 4 Sept 1950-17 Sept 1950.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1050; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks. She is wearing oval glasses, a necklace, and a jacket over her blouse.
  - Employee photo of Leland Sparks Jr., July 7, 1972; UNRS-P2017-13_1051; Photographic print; 1 1/4 x 1 1/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Headshot of Leland Sparks Jr. for and employee card. On verso: Sex - Male, July 7, 1972, Employee's Signature.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Jr. Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1052; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Faded photograph of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Sparks Jr., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1053; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Faded photograph of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin looking at each other.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Sparks Jr., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1054; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Patricia Clarkin sitting next to Leland Sparks Jr., who has his arm around her.
  - Patricia Clarkin, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1055; Photographic print; 2 1/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Patricia Clarkin sitting at a table. She has her chin propped on one hand and there is a potted plant in the background.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Sparks Jr., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1056; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Patricia Clarkin and Leland Sparks Jr. sitting at a table. Patricia has her arm around Leland's shoulder.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Jr. Sparks on their wedding day, April 10, 1948; UNRS-P2017-13_1057; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Patricia Clarkin Sparks and Leland Sparks Jr. standing outside a house on their wedding day.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 2 - Handwritten on verso: Leland/Patty Sparks Wed. Day.
  - Patricia Clarkin, Leland Jr. Sparks, best man, and maid of honor, April 10, 1948; UNRS-P2017-13_1058; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 3 1/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Patricia Clarkin and Leland Sparks Jr. standing outside a house on their wedding day. The best man and maid of honor are standing next to them.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Jr. Sparks on their wedding day, April 10, 1948; UNRS-P2017-13_1059; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 5 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Faded color photograph of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin on their wedding day. They are standing in front of a house. Faded stamp on back: April 10, 1948.
  - Patricia Clarkin, Leland Sparks Jr., best man, and maid of honor, April 10, 1948; UNRS-P2017-13_1060; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 5 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Faded color photograph of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin on their wedding day. They are standing in front of a house in between their best man and maid of honor. Faded stamp on back: T. M. Regis. U. S. Pat. Off. April 10, 1948.
  - Patricia Clarkin, Leland Jr. Sparks, best man, and maid of honor, April 10, 1948; UNRS-P2017-13_1061; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 5 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Faded color photograph of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin on their wedding day. They are standing in front of a house in between their best man and maid of honor. Faded stamp on back: Kodacolor print made by Eastman Kodak Company T. M. Regis. U. S. Pat. Off. April 10, 1948.
  - Patricia Clarkin and Leland Sparks Jr. at their wedding cake, April 10, 1948; UNRS-P2017-13_1062; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 5 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Faded color photograph of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin on their wedding day. They are looking at each other as they cut the wedding cake. Faded stamp on the back: Kodacolor print made by Eastman Kodak Company T. M. Regis. U. S. Pat. Off. April 10, 1948.
  - Patricia Clarkin Sparks, 1950; UNRS-P2017-13_1063; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Patricia Clarkin Sparks sitting in a chair in a room. There is a dorway behind and a radio on a table.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 1 - Handwritten on verso: Patty 1950.
  - Patricia Clarkin, Leland Jr. Sparks and two of their kids, 1952-1954; UNRS-P2017-13_1064; Photographic print; 7 x 5 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Leland Jr. and Patricia Sparks sitting in a chair and on a footstool. Patricia is holding a small baby and Leland is holding a young child about four years old.
  - Four of Leland Sparks Jr.’s kids, 1955-1965; UNRS-P2017-13_1065; Photographic print; 5 x 3 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of four of Leland Sparks Jr.'s kids, John, Pat, Tom, and Tony, holding pine branches. Handwritten on the photo: John, Pat, Tom, Tony.
  - Sparks family gathered around the Christmas tree, 1895-1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1066; Copy 1 - Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4; the photograph is washed out. Copy 2 - Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4; Photograph was found curled. Should eventually be rehumidified to flatten it out. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of John Sparks and his family around a Christmas tree. Identifiable people in the photograph: Leland Sparks Sr, John Sparks, Elnora Knight Sparks, Charles Sparks.
  - Sparks family sitting around a dinner table, 1895-1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1067; Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4; Photograph was found curled. Should eventually be rehumidified to flatten it out. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of the members of the Sparks family sitting around a dinner table, most likely around Christmas time. Identifiable people in the image: Leland Sparks Sr., Charles Sparks.
    There are two copies of this photograph
  - Man with four ponies, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1068; Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4; Photograph was found curled. Should eventually be rehumidified to flatten it out. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of an unidentified man standing between four shaggy ponies in a pasture. He is wearing a suit and hat. Possibly taken at the Sparks Alamo Ranch.
  - Sparks family Christmas tree, 1895-1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1069; Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4; Photograph was found curled. Should eventually be rehumidified to flatten it out. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of a Sparks family Christmas tree.
  - Two horses in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1070; Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4; Photograph was found curled. Should eventually be rehumidified to flatten it out. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of two horses standing in a field. One is an adult and the other is a young pony.
  - Sparks ranch house in Reno, Nevada, May 1903; UNRS-P2017-13_1071; Photographic print; 5 x 3 1/2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of the Sparks family ranch house in Reno, Nevada.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 2 - Handwritten on verso: Ranch home of Gov. John Sparks Reno, Nev. May '03.
  - Sparks ranch house in Reno, Nevada, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1072; Photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ruth Searles Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1073; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a young woman, possibly Ruth Searles, a potential first wife of Leland Sparks Sr., sitting at a piano. She is wearing a white dress and her hair pulled back in a loose white bow.
  - Charles Sparks and friends, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1074; Photographic print; 1 x 3 7/8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Group of three photographs depicting Charles Meigs Sparks with three of his classmates. In the top photo, the four men are looking at the camera. In the middle photo, the men on the right are looking at the camera and the others are looking off to the left fo the camera. In the bottom photo, Charles is looking at the man next to him while the bottom row is looking at the camera.
  - Small photos of a dog, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1075; Photographic print; 7/8 x 3 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Group of three photographs of a long haired daschund. In the top photo, the dog is sitting on a pedestal. In the middle photo, the dog is sitting with its front paws in the air looking to the side of the camera. In the bottom photo, the dog is sitting with its front paws in the air looking at the camera.
  - Charles Sparks, August 26, 1928; UNRS-P2017-13_1076; Photographic print; 2 3/8 x 3 1/4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Charles Meigs Sparks standing next to a saddle with a lasso around the saddle horn. Charles is wearing a cowboy hat, white shirt, and chaps. Handwritten on verso: 8/26/28.
  - Charles Sparks with a friend and a dog, 1895-1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1077; Photographic print; 4 5/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Charles Meigs Sparks standing on the lawn in front of the Sparks ranch house. He is standing next a dog and another unidentified boy. Both boys are wearing hats, pants with suspenders, and a long sleeved button down shirt.
  - Charles Sparks standing with unidentified men, 1920-1930; UNRS-P2017-13_1078; Photographic print; 5 x 3 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of six men standing in front of a doorway. The man on the far right is Charles Meigs Sparks.
  - Charles Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1079; Mounted photographic print; 1 1/4 x 1 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Portrait of Charles Meigs Sparks wearing a suit. Photographer: J.R. O'Connor.
  - Charles Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1080; Mounted photographic print; 2 x 6 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Portrait of Charles Meigs Sparks wearing a suit.
  - Charles Sparks, 1890-1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1081; Mounted photographic print; 1 1/2 x 1 7/8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Hand tinted portrait of Charles Meigs Sparks. Photographer: Thomson.
  - Charles Sparks, 1894-1904; UNRS-P2017-13_1082; Mounted photographic print; 1 3/4 x 3 1/8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Mounted portrait of Charles Meigs Sparks wearing a suit.
  - Charles Sparks with a pug and four friends, 1890-1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1083; Mounted photographic print; 5 1/2 x 2 5/8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Charles Meigs Sparks with four other unidentified boys. Charles is in the center with his hand wrapped around a pug. Photograph by the Riverside Studio.
  - Charles Sparks with a pug and four friends, 1890-1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1084; Copy 1 - Photographic print; 5 1/2 x 2 3/4 Copy 2 - Mounted photographic print; 5 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Charles Meigs Sparks with four other unidentified boys. Charles is in the center next to a pug. The other four boys surround him and are looking at each other.
  - Pug, 1890-1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1085; Mounted photographic print; 2 5/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a pug sitting on a table. The pug is looking at the camera.
  - Pug, 1890-1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1086; Mounted photographic print; 2 5/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a pug sitting on a table. The pug is looking off to the side.
  - Charles Sparks with a toy wagon, 1887-1891; UNRS-P2017-13_1087; Cabinet card; 4 1/8 x 6 3/8 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of Charles Meigs Sparks standing next to a tasselled chair. He is wearing a dark skirt and blouse while holding the handle of a toy wagon. Photographer: N. M. Wilcox.
  - Charles Sparks as a boy, 1892; UNRS-P2017-13_1088; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 3/8 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of Charles Meigs Sparks. He is wearing a suit with a loose checkered bowtie. Photographer: Snasey.
    There are two copies of this cabinet card. Copy 2 - Handwritten on verso: Charlie Sparks 1892.
  - Governor Sparks in a parade, 1895-1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1089; Mounted photographic print; 5 3/8 x 3 1/4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of John Sparks wearing a suit and riding a horse through a small town. Around him are other people also riding horses. Hand written caption on the bottom: Compliments of Mrs. J. P. O'Brian. Tonopah, Nev.
  - Elk on the Sparks Alamo Ranch, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1090; Mounted photographic print; 4 7/8 x 3 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of three elk in a pasture standing next to a feeding trough. Handwritten on verso: the Sparks. The Elk at our Alamo Ranch.
    Photograph 01471 is a duplicate of photograph 01090.
  - Ella and Holme Dickerson, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1091; Mounted photographic print; 3 3/4 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a man and woman. The man is wearing a dark colored dress and the man is wearing a suit and has a mustache. Photograph by Hofsteater. Handwritten on verso: Ella Dickerson and first husband Holme.
  - Milton Brown, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1092; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/8 x 5 5/8 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Millie Brown standing on a fur rug in a military uniform costume. Handwritten on verso: Millie Brown Carson City.
  - Allie Burwitz Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1093; Mounted photographic print; 1 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Mounted photograph of Allie Burwitz Sparks. She is wearing a dark colored dress. Handwritten on verso: Allie M. Sparks Wife of Leland John Sparks Sr.
    Photograph was attached to 00838_c2 with tape. The tape was removed so that the photographs could be sleeved separately.
  - Benton H. Sparks as a baby, 1882; UNRS-P2017-13_1094; Cabinet card; 4 1/8 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of Benton Hackett Sparks as a baby. He is wearing a white dress and sitting on a table covered with a floral cloth. Photographer: Taber. Handwritten on verso: Benton H. Sparks.
  - Leland John Sparks Sr. as a boy, 1892; UNRS-P2017-13_1095; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of Leland Sparks Sr. as a young boy. He is standing next to a couch wearing a dark suit and white loose tie. Photographer: Snasey. Handwritten on verso: Leland John Sparks Sr.
  - Leland John Sparks Sr. as a boy, 1892; UNRS-P2017-13_1096; Cabinet card; 4 1/8 x 5 3/4 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of Leland Sparks Sr. as a young boy. He is wearing a dark suit and white loose tie. Handwritten on verso: Leland Sparks, 1892, Leland John Sparks Sr.
  - Rose Burwitz, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1097; Mounted photographic print; 3 7/8 x 5 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Portrait of Rose Burwitz. She is wearing a dress with a vine over her shoulder. Handwritten on verso: Rose (Rosa) Burwitz.
  - Lillian Moore, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1098; Mounted photographic print; 3 3/8 x 4 3/8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Portrait of Lillian Moore. She is wearing a white dress with a lacy shawl. Handwritten on verso: Lillian Moore - Painter.
  - Nancy Elnora Knight Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1099; Cabinet card; 4 1/8 x 6 3/8 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of Nancy Elnora Knight Sparks. She is wearing a dress with her hair pulled back and curled on top of her head. Handwritten on verso: Nancy Elnora Sparks Wife of Gov. John Sparks. Photographer: N. M. Wilcox.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1100; Mounted photograph; 3 1/2 x 5 1/4 (Box 9)
    Portrait of Maud Mackenzie Sparks wearing a white dress. Handwritten on verso: Maud Sparks Makenzie, Maude Sparks McKenzie.
    Photograph of 01259 is a duplicate of this 01100.
  - Geronimo, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1101; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of an Native American chief wearing a buckskin shirt, feather headdress, and holding a pistol. Handwritten on verso: Geronimo. Photographer: Irwin.
  - Ada Ede as a baby, 1880-1886; UNRS-P2017-13_1102; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of Ada Ede as a baby. She is wearing a white dress and her hair is wavy. Photographer: E. P. Butler at the Reno Art Gallery studio. Handwritten on verso: Ada Ede later Ada Sparks.
  - Allie Burwitz and Jessie Dickerson, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1103; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of Allie Burwitz and Jessie Dickerson. There are two photos present: one where Allie and Jessie are holding and another where Jessie is holding a candy for Allie to eat. Handwritten on front: Allie Me Me Allie (underneath the girls in the photo). Handwritten on verso: Allie Burwitz Sparks +2 yrs old Jessie Dickerson 4 yrs old. Our mothers' were twins. My mother's name Columbia Houston Allie's mothers name America Minerva Houstin. Cousins. Photographer: O. M. Hofsteater.
  - Allie Burwitz and Margie Ostrand, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1104; Mounted photograph; 4 3/4 x 3 7/8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photograph of Allie Myrtle Burwitz and her friend Margie Ostrand. They are standing beside a house holding bicycles. Handwritten on verso: Allie Myrtle Burwitz w/ friend Margie Ostrand near Cornelius.
  - John Sparks and a man in a buggy, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1105; Mounted photograph; 3 1/4 x 3 1/4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of an unknown man and John Sparks sitting in a horse drawn buggy. Handwritten caption: John Sparks & unknown in a Tom Connoley buggy.
    Mounted to the same board as photograph 01106.
  - John Sparks and a man in a wagon, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1106; Mounted photograph; 3 1/4 x 3 1/4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Photograph of an unknown man and John Sparks riding through a field in a wagon.
    Mounted to the same board as photograph 01105.
  - John Sparks, 1875-1885; UNRS-P2017-13_1107; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of John Sparks. He is wearing a suit and bowtie. Photographer: Kirkland.
  - John Sparks, December 15, 1884; UNRS-P2017-13_1108; Cabinet card; 4 1/8 x 6 3/8 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card portrait of John Sparks. He is wearing a suit with a patterned vest and bowtie. Photographer: Kirkland. Handwritten on verso: Jno Sparks Reno Nevada/ Mrs. Nora Sparks Rietuu (?)/ Dec. 15, 1884.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie’s Spanish house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1109; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a single story house in Carmel, California. There are a lot of small trees and bushes surrounding the house. Handwritten on verso: Aunty Mauds house in Carmel The old house is of probable Spanish or Mexican origin.
  - Front entrance to Maud Sparks MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1110; Photographic print; 5 5/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of the front of Maud (Sparks) and Jim MacKenzie's house in Carmel, California. There are potted bushes in front of the doorway. Handwritten on verso: Maud & Jim MacKenzie House on the 17 mi drive just north of the Carmel gate.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie’s cat, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1111; Photographic print; 4 7/8 x 6 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a white cat sitting. There is a staircase behind it with a bowl on the bottom step. Handwritten on verso: Auntie Mauds house & cat.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie’s cat, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1112; Photographic print; 4 3/4 x 6 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a white cat sitting next to a white flower. Behind the cat is a glass door and some plants. Handwritten on verso: Auntie Mauds house & cat.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie’s cat, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1113; Photographic print; 4 3/4 x 6 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a white cat sitting next to a white flower. The cat is staring at the flower. Behind the cat is a glass door and some plants. Handwritten on verso: One of Aunty Mauds cats on patio of old Spanish house, Carmel, Calif.
  - Carmel, California, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1114; Photographic print; 6 7/8 x 4 7/8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Carmel, California, shoreline and town. Stamped on verso: Photographed by: Lewis Josselyn Carmel, California.
  - Beach in Carmel, California, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1115; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a beach in Carmel, California. Most likely taken from Maud Sparks MacKenzie's house in Carmel. Handwritten on verso: A better view of Trixie & Jim McKenzie.
  - Three horses on a beach in Carmel, California, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1116; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a beach in Carmel, California with three horses on the beach. Most likely taken from Maud Sparks MacKenzie's house in Carmel. Handwritten on verso: A good view of Mr. McKenzie and Trixie.
  - Reverend Robert MacKenzie, December 1916; UNRS-P2017-13_1117; Photographic print; 6 5/8 x 10 5/8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Portrait of Robert Mackenzie in profile. Handwritten on front: Xmas 1916. Handwritten on verso: Rev. Robert MacKenzie. Father of Jim & Jean MacKenzie.
  - Nancy Elnora, Allie, and Nancy Lee Sparks, 1921-1924; UNRS-P2017-13_1118; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 5/8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photograph of Allie Burwitz Sparks, Nancy Elnora Knight Sparks, and Nancy Lee Sparks sitting on a front lawn most likely in Berkeley, California. Behind them is a street with two story houses, a tree, and a car parked. Handwritten on verso: Allie Sparks.
  - John Sparks, Son of Benton H. Sparks, 1908-1912; UNRS-P2017-13_1119; Photographic print; 3 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of a young John Sparks, son of Benton Sparks, standing on a grassy hill. He is wearing a long coat and hat.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 1 - Handwritten on verso: John Sparks, Son of Benton & Ada Sparks.
  - John, Benton K., and Ada Sparks, 1908-1912; UNRS-P2017-13_1120; Photographic print; 3 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of Benton Hackett Sparks' wife, Ada Sparks, and kids, John and Benton Knight. John is standing on a hillside while Benton and Ada are sitting on the hill.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 1 - Handwritten on verso: l to rt. John, Benton & Ada Sparks.
  - John and Benton K. Sparks, 1908-1912; UNRS-P2017-13_1121; Photographic print; 3 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of Benton and Ada Sparks' sons, John and Benton. Both are wearing long coats and sitting on a hillside. John is looking behind the camera and Benton is distracted by something he is holding. Handwritten on verso: John (left) Benton (right) Sons of Benton & Ada Sparks.
  - John Sparks, son of Leland Jr. Sparks, April 1960; UNRS-P2017-13_1122; Photographic print; 5 x 3 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photograph of John Sparks, son of Leland Sparks Jr. and Patricia Clarkin Sparks, sitting on a slope near a road. Handwritten on verso: Johnny at Idle Acres.
  - Alfred Sparks, 1913; UNRS-P2017-13_1123; Photographic print; 3 3/4 x 5 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of Alfred Sparks, son of Benton and Ada Sparks, as a baby. He is wearing a white dress and shoes. Handwritten on front: Bann (?) 13. Handwritten on verso: Alfred Sparks.
  - Alfred Sparks, 1914-1916; UNRS-P2017-13_1124; Photographic print; 3 7/8 x 5 7/8 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of Alfred Sparks, son of Benton and Ada Sparks, as a young boy. He is wearing a sailor's shirt, shorts, and shoes with striped socks.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 1 - Handwritten on verso: Alfred Ede Sparks Son of Benton and Ada Sparks. Photograph was stored in a 4-fold envelope labeled Riverside Studios. It has been resleeved.
  - Alfred Sparks, 1913; UNRS-P2017-13_1125; Photographic print; 3 3/4 x 5 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of Alfred Sparks, son of Benton and Ada Sparks, as a baby. He is wearing a white dress and shoes. Handwritten on front: Bann (?) 13. Handwritten on verso: Alfred Sparks Benton & Ada Sparks youngest son.
  - Alfred Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1126; Photographic print; 4 5/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 1)